{
    "id": "3050e3ba2e9b47a0a6f79f7c31d76505",
    "title": "All, Whole Or Every",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I spent the ……………………………… in bed.",
            "description": "The article goes before whole.",
            "answers": [
                "whole day",
                "all day",
                "whole the day"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "06a4fefa1fd541f398ca9a3819a80aec"
        },
        {
            "question": "I spent ……………………………. the week with my parents.",
            "description": "We use all or all of before a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "all of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "deef59621f2840c78095df311f5f4961"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was here ………………………………..",
            "description": "All day means from morning to night.",
            "answers": [
                "all day",
                "whole day",
                "every day"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9715c97348f64976b0b8d91bf42ab7fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was here …………………………………… of the week.",
            "description": "Every day means Monday to Sunday.",
            "answers": [
                "all day",
                "every day",
                "every the day"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8fa7352ce8db4b809027839df68633e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly ……………………………… went out.",
            "description": "All and all of can both be used before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "all the lights",
                "all of the lights",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bf6d181f5b844d25a35b6f923c0a8691"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. Paris was talking about their affair.",
            "description": "All Paris means all parts of Paris.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All the",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "75343c4a484347b3a4f790db50d7022c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited ………………………………. friends.",
            "description": "All and all of can both be used before a pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "all my",
                "all of my",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "de5f4c26e77d40fba625274f75e89a96"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited ……………………………….. I have.",
            "description": "Before a singular noun we use every.",
            "answers": [
                "every of friend",
                "every friend",
                "all friend"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "61a63d2b3b074e87b4d64fd610bba366"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents lived their ………………………………. in Mexico.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all life",
                "whole life",
                "whole life"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8390bb712b294aac963910b98c8384fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoy ……………………………… music.",
            "description": "We cannot use every with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "all of",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f12d63f7273c43a389ff71e189c96ab7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I spent ……………………………….. the afternoon at home.",
            "description": "Instead of whole of, we generally use the whole of.",
            "answers": [
                "the whole of",
                "whole of",
                "the whole"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6953b6bfbf884eca995cf9cf3c0486d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your cat has drunk ………………………………….",
            "description": "We use all of with most uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "all the milk",
                "all of the milk"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e91184c109e45019238e5aedc11d8d4"
        }
    ]
}